{
    "subject": "Jill_Hennessy",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "The_Acting_Class",
    "human_readable": "Jill Hennessy acted in The Acting Class.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9869362711906433,
            "question": "Was Jill Hennessy involved in the film The Acting Class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9865715503692627,
            "question": "What role did Jill Hennessy play in The Acting Class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9153081774711609,
            "question": "Jill Hennessy is known for acting in which movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8066553473472595,
            "question": "Who acted in The Acting Class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.716088056564331,
            "question": "Which actress starred in The Acting Class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7145377397537231,
            "question": "In what movie did Jill Hennessy act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6700944304466248,
            "question": "What movie did Jill Hennessy appear in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48820239305496216,
            "question": "Name a film featuring Jill Hennessy."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36968347430229187,
            "question": "Name a movie that stars Jill Hennessy."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2853781580924988,
            "question": "What is the name of the film featuring Jill Hennessy's performance?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jill Hennessy acted in The Acting Class.",
            "html": "yago_5149_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a movie that stars Jill Hennessy.",
            "html": "yago_5149_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film featuring Jill Hennessy.",
            "html": "yago_5149_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What movie did Jill Hennessy appear in?",
            "html": "yago_5149_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5149_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5149_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5149_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5149_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5149_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5149_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5149_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5149_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5149_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5149_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Jill Hennessy wrote and co-directed the film \"The Acting Class,\" which directly supports the statement that she acted in it."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}